BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XVIII: Code #61, Educational Services
  - Code no.840111: Maine, University of (System) and National Education Association, 1990-1999 (Box 186, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: University of Maine System Board of Trustees and Associated C.O.L.T. Staff of the University of Maine System, National Education Association, 1990-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 186, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1990 and expires on 6/30/1992. Covers 1050 workers in Orono, ME
    - Item 2: University of Maine System Board of Trustees and Associated C.O.L.T. Staff of the University of Maine System, National Education Association, 1992-1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 186, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1992 and expires on 6/30/1995. Covers 1050 workers in Orono, ME
    - Item 3: University of Maine System Board of Trustees and Associated C.O.L.T. Staff of the University of Maine System, National Education Association, 1995-1997; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 186, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1995 and expires on 6/30/1997. Covers 1091 workers in Orono, ME
    - Item 4: University of Maine System Board of Trustees and Associated C.O.L.T. Staff of the University of Maine System, National Education Association, 1997-1999; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 186, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1997 and expires on 6/30/1999. Covers 1050 workers in Orono, ME
  - Code no.800040: Illinois, University of, Board of Trustees and College, University and School Employees Union, 1977-1995 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: University of Illinois Board of Trustees and College, University and School Employees' Union, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 321, 1977-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1977 and expires on 9/30/1978. Covers 500 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 2: University of Illinois Board of Trustees and College, University and School Employees' Union, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 321, 1980-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1980 and expires on 9/30/1981. Covers 800 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 3: University of Illinois Board of Trustees and College, University and School Employees' Union, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 321, 1981-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1981 and expires on 9/30/1982. Covers 600 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 4: University of Illinois Board of Trustees and College, University and School Employees' Union, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 321, 1984-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1984 and expires on 9/30/1986. Covers 4000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 5: University of Illinois Board of Trustees and College, University and School Employees' Union, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 321, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1986 and expires on 9/30/1989. Covers 550 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 6: University of Illinois Board of Trustees and General Service Employees Union, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 73, 1992-1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1992 and expires on 9/30/1995. Covers 740 workers in Chicago, IL
  - Code no.800171: New York, State of (faculty) and United University Professionals, 1974-1988 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: State of New York Executive Branch & State University of New York and United University Professions, Inc., 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1974 and expires on 6/30/1976. Covers 15000 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 2: State of New York Executive Branch & State University of New York and United University Professions, Inc., 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 7/17/1979 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 3: State of New York Executive Branch & State University of New York and United University Professions, Inc., 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1985. Covers 18564 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 4: State of New York Executive Branch & State University of New York and United University Professions, Inc., 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1985 and expires on 6/30/1988. Covers 17000 workers in New York, NY
  - Code no.811835: Waterbury Board of Education and Connecticut Education Association, 1982-1993 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1985. Covers 1100 workers in Waterbury, CT
    - Item 2: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1985 and expires on 6/30/1988. Covers 1100 workers in Waterbury, CT
    - Item 3: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association Addendum, 1985-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1985 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers an unknown number of workers in Waterbury, CT
    - Item 4: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association, 1989-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1989 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers an unknown number of workers in Waterbury, CT
    - Item 5: Waterbury Board of Education and Waterbury Teachers Association, Connecticut Education Association, National Education Association, 1993-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1993 and expires on 6/30/1994. Covers an unknown number of workers in Waterbury, CT
  - Code no.820791: Hillsborough County School Board and Hillsborough County Teachers Association, 1979-1986 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Hillsborough County School Board and Hillsborough Classroom Teachers Association, Inc., 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1979 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers 6400 workers in Hillsborough Co., FL
    - Item 2: Hillsborough County School Board and Hillsborough Classroom Teachers Association, Inc. Addendum, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1980 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers an unknown number of workers in Hillsborough Co., FL
    - Item 3: Hillsborough County School Board and Hillsborough Classroom Teachers Association, Inc., 1982-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 9/14/1982 and expires on 6/30/1983. Covers 6523 workers in Hillsborough Co., FL
    - Item 4: Hillsborough County School Board and Hillsborough Classroom Teachers Association, Inc. Addendum, 1982-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1983. Covers 6390 workers in Hillsborough Co., FL
    - Item 5: Hillsborough County School Board and Hillsborough Classroom Teachers Association, Inc., 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 11/19/1985 and expires on 6/30/1988. Covers 7287 workers in Hillsborough Co., FL
    - Item 6: Hillsborough County School Board and Hillsborough Classroom Teachers Association, Inc., 1985-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 11/3/1985 and expires on 10/31/1986. Covers an unknown number of workers in Hillsborough Co., FL
  - Code no.830061: Fort Worth Independent School District and National Education Association, 1966-1982 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Fort Worth Independent School District Board of Education and Fort Worth Classroom Teachers Association, 1966-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1966 and expires on 9/30/1970. Covers an unknown number of workers in Fort Worth, TX
    - Item 2: Fort Worth Independent School District Board of Education and Fort Worth Classroom Teachers Association, National Education Association, 1968-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1968 and expires on 3/31/1969. Covers an unknown number of workers in Fort Worth, TX
    - Item 3: Fort Worth Independent School District Board of Education and Fort Worth Classroom Teachers Association, 1970-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 5/27/1970 and expires on 5/1/1971. Covers an unknown number of workers in Fort Worth, TX
    - Item 4: Fort Worth Independent School District Board of Education and Fort Worth Classroom Teachers Association Addendum, 1981-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1981 and expires on 12/31/1982. Covers an unknown number of workers in Fort Worth, TX
  - Code no.830188: Indiana Board of School Commissioners and Indiana Education Association, 1978-1989 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Indianapolis Board of School Commissioners and Indianapolis Education Association, 1978-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1978 and expires on 8/31/1979. Covers an unknown number of workers in Indianapolis, IN
    - Item 2: Indianapolis Board of School Commissioners and Indianapolis Education Association, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/3/1980 and expires on 8/31/1982. Covers 3440 workers in Indianapolis, IN
    - Item 3: Indianapolis Board of School Commissioners and Indianapolis Education Association, 1982-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/31/1982 and expires on 8/31/1984. Covers 2936 workers in Indianapolis, IN
    - Item 4: Indianapolis Board of School Commissioners and Indianapolis Education Association, 1984-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/20/1984 and expires on 8/31/1985. Covers 3071 workers in Indianapolis, IN
    - Item 5: Indianapolis Board of School Commissioners and Indianapolis Education Association, 1985-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/29/1985 and expires on 8/31/1986. Covers 2892 workers in Indianapolis, IN
    - Item 6: Indianapolis Board of School Commissioners and Indianapolis Education Association, 1986-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/26/1986 and expires on 8/31/1987. Covers 3000 workers in Indianapolis, IN
    - Item 7: Indianapolis Board of School Commissioners and Indianapolis Education Association, 1987-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1987 and expires on 8/31/1989. Covers 3120 workers in Indianapolis, IN
  - Code no.830193: Cincinnati Board of Education and Cincinnati Teachers Association, 1972-1987 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Cincinnati School District Board of Education and Cincinnati Teachers Association, Ohio Education Association, National Education Association, 1972-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1972 and expires on 1/19/1974. Covers 3000 workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 2: Cincinnati School District Board of Education and Cincinnati Teachers Association, Ohio Education Association, National Education Association, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1974 and expires on 12/31/1976. Covers 3047 workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 3: Cincinnati School District Board of Education and Cincinnati Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1520, 1977-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 5/10/1977 and expires on 12/31/1979. Covers 3150 workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 4: Cincinnati School District Board of Education and Cincinnati Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1520, 1977-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 5/10/1977 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers 3500 workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 5: Cincinnati School District Board of Education and Cincinnati Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1520, 1981-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 9/17/1981 and expires on 12/31/1984. Covers 3100 workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 6: Cincinnati School District Board of Education and Cincinnati Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1520, 1985-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 3/11/1985 and expires on 12/31/1987. Covers 3200 workers in Cincinnati, OH
  - Code no.830194: Cincinnati Board of Education and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1977-1987 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Cincinnati, Ohio Board of Education and Ohio Council 8, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Locals 232, 1938, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1977 and expires on 6/30/1980. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 2: Cincinnati, Ohio Board of Education and Ohio Council 8, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Locals 232, 1938 Addendum, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 4/6/1980 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers 2000 workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 3: Cincinnati, Ohio Board of Education and Ohio Council 8, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Locals 232, 1938, 1981-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 12/31/1981 and expires on 12/31/1985. Covers 2000 workers in Cincinnati, OH
    - Item 4: Cincinnati, Ohio Board of Education and Ohio Council 8, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Locals 232, 1938, 1985-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 12/31/1985 and expires on 12/31/1987. Covers 2500 workers in Cincinnati, OH
  - Code no.830198: Montgomery County MD Board of Education and Montgomery County Education Association, 1977-1992 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Montgomery County Board of Education and Montgomery County Education Association, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1977 and expires on 6/30/1980. Covers 7000 workers in Montgomery Co., MD
    - Item 2: Montgomery County Board of Education and Montgomery County Education Association, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1980 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers 7000 workers in Montgomery Co., MD
    - Item 3: Montgomery County Board of Education and Montgomery County Education Association, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 8/31/1984 and expires on 6/30/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Montgomery Co., MD
    - Item 4: Montgomery County Board of Education and Montgomery County Education Association, 1987-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1987 and expires on 6/30/1990. Covers 6000 workers in Montgomery Co., MD
    - Item 5: Montgomery County Board of Education and Montgomery County Education Association, 1990-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1990 and expires on 6/30/1992. Covers 7463 workers in Montgomery Co., MD
  - Code no.830213: Phoenix Board of Education (Professionals) and Education Association, 1979-1989 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and Classroom Teachers Association, 1979-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1979 and expires on 6/30/1980. Covers 1400 workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 2: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and Classroom Teachers Association, 1980-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1980 and expires on 6/30/1981. Covers 1100 workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 3: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and Classroom Teachers Association, 1981-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1981 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers an unknown number of workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 4: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and Classroom Teachers Association, 1983-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1983 and expires on 6/30/1984. Covers 1100 workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 5: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and Classroom Teachers Association, 1984-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1984 and expires on 6/30/1985. Covers 1081 workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 6: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and "Representative Groups", 1985-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1985 and expires on 6/30/1986. Covers 1080 workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 7: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and "Representative Groups", 1986-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1986 and expires on 6/30/1987. Covers 1056 workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 8: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and No union specified Memorandum, 1986-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1986 and expires on 6/30/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 9: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and Classroom Teachers Association, 1987-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1987 and expires on 6/30/1988. Covers 1100 workers in Phoenix, AZ
    - Item 10: Phoenix Union High School District No. 210 and Classroom Teachers Association, 1988-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1988 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers 1214 workers in Phoenix, AZ
  - Code no.830239: Columbus Board of Education and Columbus Education Association, 1976-1986 (Box 187, Folder 11)
    1976-1981, 1983-1986
    - Item 1: Columbus Board of Education of the Columbus City School District and Columbus Education Association, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1976 and expires on 8/31/1979. Covers 5000 workers in Columbus, OH
    - Item 2: Columbus Board of Education of the Columbus City School District and Columbus Education Association, 1979-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1979 and expires on 8/31/1981. Covers 4500 workers in Columbus, OH
    - Item 3: Columbus Board of Education of the Columbus City School District and Columbus Education Association, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1983 and expires on 8/24/1986. Covers 4500 workers in Columbus, OH
  - Code no.830280: Seattle School District and Seattle Teachers Association, 1977-1985 (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Seattle School District No. 1 and Seattle Teachers Association, 1977-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1977 and expires on 6/30/1979. Covers 3357 workers in Seattle, WA
    - Item 2: Seattle School District No. 1 and Seattle Teachers Association, 1979-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1979 and expires on 6/30/1981. Covers 3000 workers in Seattle, WA
    - Item 3: Seattle School District No. 1 and Seattle Teachers Association, 1983-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1983 and expires on 8/31/1985. Covers an unknown number of workers in Seattle, WA
  - Code no.830301: Lansing Board of Education and Lansing State Educational Association, 1979-1987 (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Lansing School District Board of Education and Lansing Schools Education Association, 1979-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 10/5/1979 and expires on 7/31/1981. Covers 1540 workers in Lansing, MI
    - Item 2: Lansing School District Board of Education and Lansing Schools Education Association, 1981-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 9/8/1981 and expires on 7/31/1984. Covers 1500 workers in Lansing, MI
    - Item 3: Lansing School District Board of Education and Lansing Schools Education Association, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1984 and expires on 7/31/1987. Covers 1307 workers in Lansing, MI
  - Code no.830311: Denver School District and Colorado Teachers Association, 1980-1990 (Box 187, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: City and County of Denver and State of Colorado School District No. 1 and Denver Classroom Teachers Association, 1980-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1980 and expires on 4/6/1981. Covers 4200 workers in Denver, CO
    - Item 2: City and County of Denver and State of Colorado School District No. 1 and Denver Classroom Teachers Association, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 6/15/1982 and expires on 12/31/1985. Covers 4146 workers in Denver, CO
    - Item 3: City and County of Denver and State of Colorado School District No. 1 and Denver Classroom Teachers Association Addendum, 1984-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1984 and expires on 12/31/1984. Covers 3500 workers in Denver, CO
    - Item 4: City and County of Denver and State of Colorado School District No. 1 and Denver Classroom Teachers Association, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 6/11/1985 and expires on 12/31/1988. Covers 3600 workers in Denver, CO
    - Item 5: City and County of Denver and State of Colorado School District No. 1 and Denver Classroom Teachers Association Addendum, 1986-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 187, Folder 14)